<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://www.jakeapple.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://www.jakeapple.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-08T16:31:53-05:00</updated><id>http://www.jakeapple.com/</id><title type="html">The Personal Website of Jake Apple</title><subtitle>All things Jake Apple. Mostly mundane.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why?</title><link href="http://www.jakeapple.com/blog/why" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why?" /><published>2017-05-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-05-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://www.jakeapple.com/blog/why</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.jakeapple.com/blog/why">&lt;p&gt;There are a billion blogs out there. Does the internet really need another?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, probably not. But I’m going to try anyway. Here’s why…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spend a lot of time learning on the internet. Because of the internet I have learned how to fix carburetors, take apart Macs, install water-powered sump pumps, make websites, diagnose and replace the heating coil in a dryer, build a Nicholson workbench, and so much more. The only reason I was able to do those things is becuase someone put them out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve taken a lot from my online peers, but rarely have I given back. I think I’m finally ready to contribute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;defining-success&quot;&gt;Defining Success&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to make sure I’m not wasting my energy though. If I want to add to the fabric of the internet, but no one &lt;del&gt;learns anything&lt;/del&gt; even visits, it was a bust. I’d probably be better off putting my energy elsewhere. I don’t want that to happen. So I’m going to try this out until the end of the year. Like a mid-year resolution, so to speak. I just have to make sure I can stay on track. Thankfully, a lot of other people have already figured out how to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&quot;http://secondstreet.com&quot;&gt;Secondstreet&lt;/a&gt;, we’ve adopted (and modified) the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rework.withgoogle.com/guides/set-goals-with-okrs/steps/introduction/&quot;&gt;OKR system&lt;/a&gt; that Google uses. So I’m going to lay out my Objectives and Key Results for this blog. It’s the only way I know how to determine my success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;objectives&quot;&gt;Objectives&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be first when Googling ‘jake apple’&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have this blog be considered worthy of syndication at &lt;a href=&quot;https://unpluggedshop.com&quot;&gt;unpluggedshop.com&lt;/a&gt; by December 2017&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TBD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="posts" /></entry></feed>